davidsprom.com 2017-12-12

# David's Bridal: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Rights**

Our privacy policy has changed. This privacy policy is effective as of March 1, 2017.

David's Bridal, Inc., a Florida corporation, David's Bridal Canada Inc, a Canadian national corporation, and their respective divisions, subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "David's Bridal", "we", "us", or "our") are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. We have adopted the following privacy policy to explain our practices relating to the information we collect, and the information you provide to us, through your completion of a registration or other form in one of our retail stores, and from your visit to and use of Web sites, and other mobile applications, content and services (collectively, the "Service") we make publicly available. 

* * *

This privacy policy answers the following questions, which we believe are the questions you are most likely to have about our handling of your personal information:

A.    California Privacy Rights. 

B.    What information does David's Bridal collect?

C.    How does David's Bridal use the information it collects?

D.    Will David's Bridal disclose my personal information?

E.    How can I review and revise my personal information?

F.    How can I opt-out of receiving advertising communications from David's Bridal and others? 

G.    How does David's Bridal protect my personal information?

H.    Is there anything else I should know about Internet privacy?

We review this policy regularly, and make changes in connection with its review. Please check this privacy policy page periodically for changes. Your submission of a registration form or your continued use of the Service following the posting of changes to this privacy policy means that you have accepted those changes.

* * *

 **Personal Information**

For purposes of this privacy policy, "personal information" means information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, postal address, mobile and wired telephone numbers, e-mail address, and credit card number. Personal information also includes demographic information (e.g., identity of bride or groom, date and location of the wedding, and other biographical and demographic information), location information (e.g., zip code, fine location information), and other information about a specific individual, once it is associated with personal information. However, personal information does NOT include information that we collect but do not associate with you and your personal information.

    A.   Your California Privacy Rights

David's Bridal makes these disclosures to its customers, and those visiting its website, who reside in California and supersedes and replaces any conflicting disclosures found elsewhere on our website. 

  1. _Opt-Out of Disclosure for Direct Marketing Purposes_. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes or to learn the categories of recipients and information disclosed. You may make such a request by contacting us by e-mail addressed to [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com). Please reference California Privacy Rights in your subject line. You may also write to us at David's Bridal, Inc., PO Box 549, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Privacy Officer. Please be aware that this opt-out does not prohibit our disclosure of personal information for any purpose other than direct marketing.
  2.  _Automatic Gathering of Information by David's Bridal_. David's Bridal collects information that you provide to us online, through completion of registration and other forms in our retail stores, or through other means.
  3.  _Automatic Gathering of Information by Third Parties_. When you visit our website, third parties can collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites pertaining to your visit to or use of our and other Websites. 
  4. _Do-Not-Track Requests_. As of January 1, 2014, California residents visiting our website may request that we not automatically gather and track information pertaining to their online browsing movements across the Internet. Such requests are typically made through Web browser settings that control signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party Websites or online services. David's Bridal honors these requests/settings.

Effective December 2013

    B.  What information does David's Bridal collect?

Information You Give Us: David's Bridal collects information that you provide to us online, through completion of registration and other forms in our retail stores, or through other means.

For example:

  * If you join our registry or request an appointment through the Service, we will collect your first and last name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number, specific bridal party and wedding information, and other preferences and demographic information you provide.
  * If you make a purchase through the Service, we will ask you to register with us, and we will also ask you for your credit card number, a shipping address and a telephone number for that shipping address, and for any additional information that may be required to personalize the product you purchase.
  * If you contact our customer service, we will ask you for your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, order number and such other information as you wish to submit to us to allow us to assist you.
  * If you submit a wedding, prom or special occasion story through the Service, we will ask you for your e-mail address, the names of the bride and groom or the subject of the story, the date and location of the wedding, prom or celebration of the special occasion, and such other information as you may include in the story and photos that you submit to us.
  * If you use the wedding planning section of the Service, we will also ask you to provide us with your zip code or city and state or province, if applicable.
  * If you enter our "gown giveaway", "tuxedo giveaway", "prom dress giveaway" or other contests and sweepstakes, complete our surveys, or voluntarily participate in other promotions offered by us or third parties through the Service (collectively, "Contests") we will ask you to provide personal information, such as your first and last name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number.
  * If you send us a text message, we will collect the mobile phone number you use to send us a text message, the content of the message, and we will log the wireless telecommunications service provider associated with the number and the date and time of the message.
  * Please note that registration is required to browse our online catalogs, make a purchase, post a product review, submit a story, or use certain other features of the Service, such as the "My Favorites", "MyEvent" and "Dress Your Wedding" features. 

_Social Networks_ :If you are a member of Facebook or another social network or service, and you use functionality available through the Service or otherwise authorize us to associate your Service account with that network or service, both we and the network or service will gather information about your behavior on the Service, and may associate that information with personal information we and the network or service already have about you.

 _Public Conduct_ :If you engage in behavior at or through the Service that is intended to be viewed by other users (collectively, "Public Conduct"), such as participating in forums, message boards and chat rooms; using your Facebook page, Twitter® account or other functionality available through the Service to share product preferences, comment on products and other content; creating a MyEvent page, or posting stories about your wedding, prom or other special occasion to the Service, we and others may collect information about you as a result of your Public Conduct, and all such information will be publicly available to anyone visiting or using the Service.

 _Automatic Gathering of Information_ :We and other companies and individuals we select to provide us with goods and services (each, a "Service Provider") collect non-identifying information about your visit to or use of the Service, your Web browsing movements across the Internet (not just on the Service), and your interaction with our advertisements at the Service and elsewhere. For example, we may keep track of how many of our advertisements you saw before visiting the Service, how you were directed to the Service, how you navigate around the Service, which products you browse, as well as your purchasing activities through the Service.

To do this, we and our Service Providers use technology (e.g., cookies, action tags, Web beacons, and GIF tags), placed at various sections within the Service and in our advertisements delivered by e-mail or served during your Web browsing session. Some of this technology may be disabled by changing your Web browser settings. Please consult the documentation for your Web browser on how to manage the information gathering and storage aspects of this technology on your computer. We and our Service Providers do not collect any personal information through the use of this technology.

If you use the mobile application portion of the Service, we and our Service Providers may also use various technology (e.g., anonymous identifiers, flash cookies, HTML5 software, local storage, and mini-databases) to track your Web browsing movements at the Service and across the Internet, and may store such information on your mobile device. Many mobile devices have this technology pre-loaded or incorporated in the Web browser, or the technology may be included in the mobile application you download and use on your device. Please consult your device documentation on how to manage the information gathering and storage aspects of this technology. We and our Service Providers do not collect any personal information through the use of this technology.

If you choose to reject all cookies, anonymous identifiers or similar technology, you may be unable to use much of the functionality of the Service.

Unless we associate non-identifying information that we gather through use of technology with your personal information, we will NOT treat such information as personal information.

 _Information from Other Sources_ :We may also collect information (including personal information) about you from our Service Providers and other third parties and add it to the personal information we maintain.

    C.  How does David's Bridal use the information it collects?

 _Request Fulfillment_ :We use your personal information to confirm, fulfill and ship your orders, to set up appointments that you request, to confirm your entry in our Contests, and to otherwise respond to your requests. We may also use your personal information to contact you if we want to communicate with you about your order, appointment or other request.

We may match personal information we have collected from your prior on-line or in-store interactions with us (i.e., completion of a survey or sweepstakes entry) with the personal information you enter when you complete our in-store electronic registration form to speed up the registration process and improve your in-store and on-line experience with us.

 _Promotional Messages_ : We may also use your personal information tosend you newsletters, information about special events, e-mail offers, textmessage offers, and other savings opportunities; to notify you of changes tothe Service; to provide you with up-to-date information on the newest David'sBridal products and services that may be of interest to you; to handle billingdisputes with you; and to tailor our online offerings and advertisements toyour preferences. We may also use non-identifying information about your visits to the Service and other Web sites in order to provide you with special offers about goods and services ofinterest to you, make sure you are not shown the same content repeatedly on theService, deliver information that is specific to your interests, and to saveyour password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Service.

 _Rewards Programs and Advertisements_ :We may also participate in rewards programswith other business organizations where our customers who are also members ofthese programs receive a reward from the other businesses for their purchases fromDavid's Bridal. We also placeadvertisements for our products on other Web sites that include a link enablingvisitors to click on the link to be taken to the Service and purchase theproducts featured in the advertisement. Inthese situations, we share your personal information about your purchases with theother member organizations or Web sites under the contracts these entities havewith us.

 _Optional Features_ :If you choose to participate in certain otherfeatures or functions available through the Service, such as customer service,product reviews, wish-lists, and special occasion stories or other PublicConduct, we will use your personal information to administer and operate thosefeatures and functions. We may alsoaggregate information we gather from your Public Conduct with other informationwe collect from your use of the Service.

 _Other Business Purposes_ :We may also use personal information,non-identifying information, and aggregated information about our customers'access and navigation of the Service and their browsing and purchasingactivities that we and our Service Providers obtain from our use of technology,to improve the Service, and for other business purposes, such as marketing,advertising and research. 

    D.  Will David's Bridal disclose my personal information?

 _Retail Stores_ : Our retail stores share with us the personalinformation they collect from your completion of a registration or other form, andwe combine it with the information we collect from you through the Service, sothat the Service will be able to provide you with relevant informationregarding special events and offers. Weshare the personal information we collect from you through your use of theService with our retail stores so that they can provide you with relevantinformation regarding special events and offers.

 _Service Providers_ : We engage Service Providers from time to timeto perform business functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders,delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, maintaining customerlists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, andproviding customer service. We furnishpersonal information to our Service Providers as required to perform thesebusiness functions on our behalf.

We also engage advertising agencies and other ServiceProviders and share non-identifying information and aggregated information withthem for purposes of analysis and improvement of the Service. In addition, we have carefully selectedcertain Service Providers to provide us with digital analytics and marketingoptimization services. These ServiceProviders use technology, such as cookies and anonymous identifiers, to collectinformation on our behalf that will educate us on such things as search enginereferral, how you navigate around the Service, unique visitor identification,and product browsing and purchasing information. These Service Providers are not permitted tocollect credit card, username or password information. These Service Providers analyze theinformation collected on our behalf and return it to us through a secure webconnection for our use in understanding your use of the Service and how tobetter serve you. These ServiceProviders are contractually prohibited from using our information for any otherpurpose and are required to maintain all information collected and theiranalyses in strictest confidence. Youmay choose to continue to benefit from the improved experience with the Servicethat such analyses provide to you, but maintain your anonymity. You may also choose to deactivate the abilityof these Service Providers to analyze your browsing and purchasing behavior atthe Service by setting your Web browser to reject cookies and other technology. 

_Third Parties_ :  David's Bridal may share your personal information with our formalwear partners including Men's Wearhouse, Jos. A. Bank, and Moores Clothing for Men, for direct marketing purposes. David's Bridal may also choose to share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to other third parties for direct marketing purposes (i.e., offering goods and services that we believe would be attractive to our customers). We require all third parties with whom we share information (including personal information) that we collect to handle that information in accordance with this privacy policy. However, these third parties may also have additional or different privacy practices that you may find on their respective Web sites. You may also go to their Web sites to find out more about technology they use to collect information while providing us with services.

We also may share non-identifying and aggregate information with third parties that advertise at or through the Service. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X-number of individuals visited a certain area of the Service, or that Y-number of women who filled out our registration form are from the northeast U.S., but we will not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

 _Optional Features_ : If you use optional features or functionsavailable through the Service to engage in Public Conduct, any personalinformation that you post or submit may also be collected and used by otherusers of these features to send you marketing messages and for otherpurposes. In addition, we may forwardthe information you provide as a part of Public Conduct to other Web sites as apart of an RSS feed, API, or other format.We are not responsible for editing or removing any personal informationthat you post or submit as a result of your Public Conduct. Additionally, we share personal informationabout you when you voluntarily use certain optional features of the Service. For example, if you include personalinformation in a product review that you submit, the content of that reviewwill be posted on the Service and may be distributed and posted to other Websites. If you are a member of a thirdparty rewards program, we will share personal information concerning yourpurchases through the Service with that organization. If you participate in a Contest, we will sharethe personal information you submit with our Service Providers assisting us inthe administration of the Contest.

 _Law Enforcement_ : From time to time, we may be required todisclose your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena,government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to shareinformation with law enforcement agencies concerning any activities that we, ingood faith, believe to be unlawful. Wealso may share certain personal information when we believe that such sharingis reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of othersand ourselves.

 _Business Transfers_ : Wemay also share personal information with third parties in relation to plannedor potential corporate sales, mergers, reorganizations, consolidations,dissolutions, bankruptcies or similar events.As a part of any such transaction, we will treat your personalinformation as an asset and transfer it to the purchaser.

    E.  How can I review and revise my personal information?

You may always review your Service account profile andupdate it by going to the My Account area of the Service and clicking on MyProfile. You may also modify certainpersonal information, such as your billing address, shipping address or paymentmethod, when you check out.

Our customer service representatives are also ready toassist you in checking or changing your personal profile. You may reach our customer service representativesby completing the form available on the "Contact Us" page of the"Help" section of www.DavidsBridal.com, or by sending an e-mail to usat [customerservice@dbi.com](mailto:customerservice@dbi.com). In order toensure that our Canadian customers receive a prompt response to any inquiriesregarding the review and revision of any personal information we have collected,please follow the procedures set out in the section below entitled, "ANote to Residents of Canada".

Please note that you may not access or changenon-identifying information that we collect from visitors to the Servicethrough use of technology or otherwise.

    F.  How can I opt-out of receiving advertising communications from David's Bridal and others?

You may request that we remove you from our telephonemarketing list and refrain from sharing your telephone number with thirdparties by sending usan e-mail addressed to [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com).Please reference Telephone List Removal in your subject line and includeyour telephone numbers in the body of your email. You may also write to us at David'sBridal, Inc., 1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Customer Service/Privacy.

You may request that we remove you from our postal mailinglist and refrain from sharing your postal address with third parties by sending usan e-mail addressed to [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com).Please reference Postal Mailing List Removal in your subject line andinclude your postal mailing address in the body of your email. You may also write to us at David's Bridal,Inc., 1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Customer Service/Privacy. 

If you would prefer not to receive our e-mail offers, pleaseclick on the "unsubscribe" link or follow the instructions in oure-mail message, or by sending usan e-mail addressed to [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com).Please reference E-mail List Removal in your subject line and includeyour email address in the body of the email.You may also write to us at David's Bridal, Inc., 1001 WashingtonStreet, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Customer Service/Privacy.

To opt out of text messages from David's Bridal, reply tothe text message you received with the word STOP. 

It may take David's Bridal up to thirty (30) days to implement your request that we not contact you by telephone with promotional communications. Similarly, it may take us up to ten (10) business days to implement your preference that we not transmit emails to you containing promotional offers. We will promptly communicate your preferences concerning advertising communications to the third parties with whom we have shared your contact information . However, if these third parties have personal information directly from you or from a source other than David's Bridal, you will have to opt-out from receiving their advertising communications by contacting them directly. 

From time to time, we may also use your personal informationto send important notices, such as notifications about your Service account,changes to our terms of use, this privacy policy, or other policies oragreements relevant to you, or regarding transactions or services you havespecifically requested. Because thisinformation is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt-out ofreceiving these communications. 

    G.  How does David's Bridal protect my personal information?

We take precautions to protect the personal information wecollect. We have implemented commerciallyreasonable physical, technological, and administrative procedures to safeguardand secure the personal information we collect. 

When you make a purchase through the Service, we offer theuse of a secure server. We also useSecure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology to encrypt your order informationwhen you send it to us; however, your Web browser must support the use of SSL technology. To learn more about SSL, please follow thislink to http://www.ssl.com. In addition,we use other means, such as firewalls, to safeguard the confidentiality of thisinformation. However, no method of transmissionor electronic storage provides certainty of security. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolutesecurity of the information that we collect. 

    H.  Is there anything else I should know about Internet privacy?

 **A note concerning Third Party Web sites** :

The Service may contain links to Web sites operated by thirdparties, including Web sites operated by our advertisers, Service Providers,and other business associates of David's Bridal. When you click on one of these links, youwill visit the Web sites operated by these third parties. Any information that you submit at these thirdparty Web sites are submitted by you directly to these third parties, and allsuch information will be governed by their privacy policies and procedures, notours. The privacy policies of other Websites will vary, and some may have no stated privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacypolicies or procedures of third party Web sites.

 **A note to residents of the European Union and other countries outside the United States:**

David's Bridal is located in the United States and makes theService publicly available from the United States. Any information that you provide to us will betransferred out of your country of residence to the United States. By providing personal information to us, youare consenting to its transfer to and storage in the United States and to itsuse and disclosure as described in this privacy policy. Please note that the privacy laws of the United States may offer different levels of protection from those in your country of residence and personal information may be subject to access by and disclosure to law enforcement agencies in the United States.

David's Bridal does not fulfill product orders from outsidethe United States through the Service or by telephone. If you attempt to make a purchase through theService from outside the United States, and you reside in a country that isserviced for us by our partner, Borderfree, Inc. (who also does business under the name "FiftyOne" or "E4X"), we will refer the order to Borderfree for collection ofpayment for, and fulfillment of, the order, at which time you will be requiredto submit certain credit card and other personal information to Borderfree to completeyour order.

We do, however, require that customers residing outside theUnited States create an account with David's Bridal in order to make a purchasefrom Borderfree. To create that account, we askyou for certain personal information, including your first and last names,street address, telephone number, e-mail address and wedding or other eventdate. We provide your personalinformation to Borderfree so that it may fulfill your order. Please note that Borderfree maintains its own data protectionpractices.

We will also collect other personal information that youchoose to provide to us or to Borderfree. Forexample, if you contact our customer service, we will ask you for your name,postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, order number and such otherinformation as you wish to submit to us for our assistance. You may elect at any time not to providepersonal information to us, but in that event you may not be able to make apurchase of our products from Borderfree. 

Any personal information you provide us is controlled andprocessed by David's Bridal, Inc., 1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA19428, or its suppliers. Your personalinformation provided at checkout will be controlled and processed by Borderfree, Inc.,55 West 39th Street, 18th Floor, New York, New York 10018.

 **A note to residents of Canada:**

When you visit a David's Bridal store in Canada and providepersonal information to the store or provide personal information through theService, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your personalinformation in accordance with this policy. When you provide us with information aboutyour groom or bridal party, we expect you have obtained consent from them to doso and that they understand their information will be treated in accordancewith this policy and may be shared with Moores, The Suit People, Inc. d/b/aMoores Clothing for Men. Do not providepersonal information to us about your groom or bridal party if you do not havetheir consent. You understand that by providing information about your groom or bridal party, you are representing that you have a personal or family relationship with them, and that you are requesting they be sent information, as set out above, on your behalf. This information may identify that you had requested it be sent. As explained above,because David's Bridal operates in the United States, any information providedthrough the Service or through a store in Canada may be processed in the UnitedStates, where privacy laws may offer different levels of protection from thosein Canada and personal information may be subject to access by and disclosureto law enforcement agencies in the United States.

David's Bridal provides you with the ability to access andreview your personal information held by us and will endeavor to provide theinformation in question within a reasonable time following your writtenrequest, but no later than 30 days following your written request. We will provide information from our recordsin a form that is easy to understand. Wemay charge a reasonable cost (e.g. photocopying, mail charges) when a requestis made. David's Bridal may refuse toprovide access to personal information where the information requested:

>   1. Would disclose (i) personal information of another individual or a deceased individual; or (ii) trade secrets or other confidential business information that may harm David's Bridal or the competitive position of a third party or interfere with contractual or other negotiations of David's Bridal or a third party or result in a significant financial loss or gain to David's Bridal or a third party; 
>   2. Is not readily retrievable and the burden or cost of providing would be disproportionate to the nature or value of the information; 
>   3. Is subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilege; 
>   4. Does not exist, is not held, or cannot be found by David's Bridal; 
>   5. Could reasonably result in serious harm to the treatment or recovery of the individual concerned or another individual, serious emotional harm to the individual or another individual or serious bodily harm to the individual or another individual; 
>   6. May harm or interfere with law enforcement activities and other investigative or regulatory functions of a body authorized by law to perform such functions, or; 
>   7. Any other grounds under applicable legislation.
> 

Where information will not or cannot be disclosed, theindividual making the request will be provided with the reasons fornon-disclosure.

David's Bridal will not respond to repetitive or vexatiousrequests for access. To guard againstfraudulent requests for access, David's Bridal may require sufficient informationto allow it to confirm the identity of the person making the request beforegranting access. Requests for accessshould be submitted to us by e-mail at [privacyCA@dbi.com](mailto:privacyCA@dbi.com) or by writing to us atDavid's Bridal, Inc., P.O. Box 549, Conshohocken, PA 19428, U.S.A., Attn: Privacy Officer. 

**A special note concerning children's privacy:**

The safety of children is very important to us. We are committed to protecting children'sprivacy on the Internet and we comply fully with the Children's Online PrivacyProtection Act. We do not knowinglycollect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a child has provided us with personalinformation through the Service or otherwise, we ask that a parent or guardiansend us an e-mail at [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com), or write to us at David's Bridal, Inc., 1001Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Privacy Officer, and we willdelete the information about the child from our files. Please refer to Children's Privacy in yoursubject line. Deletion requests from ourCanadian customers should be submitted to us by e-mail at [privacyCA@dbi.com](mailto:privacyCA@dbi.com) orby writing to us at David's Bridal, Inc., 1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, U.S.A., Attn: Customer Service/Privacy.

 **A note concerning changes to our privacy policy:**

By using the Service, you consent to our collection, use,and disclosure of your personal information you provide in accordance with thisprivacy policy. If we decide to changeour privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are alwaysaware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under whatcircumstances we disclose it. Privacy policy changes will apply to theinformation collected from the date we post our revised privacy policy, as wellas to existing information we hold.

 **How to contact us:**

If you have other questions, concerns or would like torequest prior versions of our privacy policy, please write us at: David'sBridal, Inc., 1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Customer Service/Privacy. 

If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you mayrequest that we remove your personal information from our records by sending usan e-mail at [remove@dbi.com](mailto:remove@dbi.com) or write us at:1001 Washington Street, Conshohocken, PA 19428, Attn: Customer Service/Privacy. 

Our Canadian customers may e-mail us at removeCA@dbi.com or write to us at: PrivacyOfficer, David's Bridal, P.O. Box 549, Conshohocken, PA 19428, U.S.A.

© 2002 - 2017 David's Bridal, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
